In the window, double-click to open the Project Files folder.
Find the G.Adding Paddings file in C.Details.
Double-click on the Jacket Padding file, or drag it to the 3D or 2D window.
In the 2D tool bar, select the Edit Files tool.
Right-click on the bottom line in the front and back.
In the
Inputs, select .
Click .
In the window,
select the Line Tool.
In the 2D window,
draw a right-angle line on the sleeve.
Use the Edit Files tool to click on the newly created line.
Press Ctrl-Z on the keyboard to copy it.
Press Ctrl-Z to paste.
The copied line will move with the mouse.
Right-click to select the menu.
Enter the number and click OK.
All newly created lines will be highlighted in yellow.
This means they are in the selected state.
Select the Edit Files tool or Edit Files tool.
Click .
In the selected internal line,
right-click on it.
In the menu,
select .
In the 2D tool bar,
select the 5th one.
Click .
Use the Edit Files tool to select the newly created internal line.
Make sure all the internal lines are in the selected frame.
Press Ctrl-C to copy the internal line.
Then press Ctrl-R to paste.
At this time, the outline of the copied internal line will move with the mouse.
Right-click on the sleeve.
In the newly added internal line, right-click.
Select the
Double-click to open the FABRIK folder and press the left button on the Nylon Featherweight file to drag it to the FABRIK 1 object window.
Press the FABRIK button to open the FABRIK 1 object window and drag it to the FABRIK 1 object window.
In the 2D window, select the outer layer of the shell and adjust the pressure to 20.
Select the inner layer of the shell.
In the
Press the FABRIK button to open the FABRIK 1 object window and drag it to the FABRIK 1 object window.
Open the model and apply the settings to the 3D model.
Apply the settings to the 3D model and apply the settings to the 3D model.